https://carolkent.com/privacy-policy/

About
Why Carol Kent?
Services
How we make it easy!
Yacht Charter FAQs
Travel Agent Partners
Gift Certficates
More Info
How Much Does it Cost to Charter a Yacht?
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Policy for Carol Kent Yacht Charters, a division of Boston Marine Services, Inc.  We are committed to the utmost of privacy for you, while you are using our online Search features or choosing a yacht vacation.
1. Contact information.
We may collect your name, street address, telephone number and/or email address.
Payment information
We may request your credit card number to apply toward your partial non-refundable deposit for your charter yacht vacation. You will be required to complete this credit card form with your agreement and signature.  We add your personal details to our sales database when you contact us.  We do not store your credit card information. If printed, it is shredded. If it is in our computer, we delete it quarterly during the calendar year.
Demographic information
We may collect information such as your gender, age and zip code to better target correspondence we send you. This may be gathered when you contact us or complete a survey.
Other information
If you use our website, we may gather information about the browser you’re using and your IP address. There is a slight possibility we will look to see which site you previously visited or the one you search when you leave us. This is unlikely, however, since we count on repeat and referral business and are not an Internet-based Charter Company.
2. We collect information in different ways.
We may gather information about you from third parties. For example, our business partners may give us information about you that we add to what you provide us.
3. We use information as disclosed and described here.
We use information to respond to your requests or questions.
For example, we might use your information to respond to your customer feedback. We may use your information to notify you if you make a purchase.
We use information to improve our products and services.
We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. We may do this by looking at site trends or customer interests.
We use information for security purposes.
We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our website.
We use information for marketing purposes.
For example, we might send you information about new products/services and special promotions. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting.
We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.
We may contact you about your order or to obtain feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.
We use information as otherwise described or permitted by law.
You have certain choices about our marketing and tracking tools.
You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.
To stop receiving our promotional emails, simply send us an email (or email marketing program) with the subject “Unsubscribe;” write to us at the below address (include your email address); or use the unsubscribe function in any promotional message you get from us. Even if you opt out of getting our marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions and order confirmations.
You can control cookies and tracking tools.
We do not use tracking tools when you visit our site. We are discrete when working with our clients and believe your privacy is just that – private. For more information please read about TOR PROJECT (based in Cambridge, Massachusetts USA).
4. These sites and children.
Our site is meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us… You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children’s privacy online COPPA ( Children’s Online Protection Rule).
5. We use standard security measures.
The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our site will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.
6. We store information in the United States.
Information we maintain will be stored within the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States.
7. We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don’t control.
If you click on a link to a third- party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully, as we are not responsible for them and their content. Our site may also serve third-party content that contains cookies or tracking technologies. We do not control the use of those technologies.
8. Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.
If you have any questions about this Policy or other privacy concerns, please email us at: info@carolkent.com.
You can also write to us or call at:
Carol Kent Yacht Charters, a division of Boston Marine Services, Inc.
144 Pleasant Street
Marblehead, Massachusetts 01945 USA
Phone: (781) 631-1800
9. We may update this Policy.
From time to time, we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.
© 2017 Carol Kent Yacht Charters, a division of Boston Marine Services, Inc. All rights reserved.
Enquire Today
Yacht Search
Home
About
Why Carol Kent?
How we make it easy!
